Sevrus Jr. Abella

≥ sevrus07@gmail.com **≥** 09928445871

Full-stack Web-based Development

🗣 Insiang Goriong Hills, Salvador Ext., Labangon, Cebu City, Philippines, 6000 Cebu

Summary

Innovative, task-driven professional with a year of experience in photo editing across diverse designs for various projects and clients. Seek to use my skill and knowledge to provide an efficient and creative way for your projects or clients.

Education

Uplift Code Camp, Cebu	
Bachelor of Science in Electronics Engineering Cebu Institute of Technology - University, Cebu	2013 - 2019
Secondary Education Don Bosco Technology Center, Cebu	2009 - 2013
Primary Education Don Bosco Technology Center, Cebu	2002 - 2009

Employment

Photo Editor 2021 - Present

Freelance

- Maintain a high level of skill and eye for detail to select, retouch and edit high-quality stock images or when producing composite images from scratch.
- Manage timelines for photo editing process between curating, editing, labeling, approving, uploading, reediting, and archiving.
- Collaborate with clients and personnel in an effective and professional manner.

Customer Sales Representative

2019 - 2020

Apr 2022 - Present

Sykes Inc., Cebu

- Resolve customer inquiries and problems by clarifying the issue, explaining the best solution and following up with their new or updated webpage.
- Handled an average of 100 inquiries in any given week and consistently met performance benchmarks in all areas (speed, accuracy and volume).
- Kept accurate record of customer interactions and corresponding cases.

Personal details

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/sevrusabella

Skills

Photo Editing

AutoCAD

HTML5

CSS3

Javascript

Python

Team Player

Leadership